genapsys.com 2019-08-15

# Genapsys: Home

**GenapSys, Inc. Privacy Policy**

Revised 6/23/2015

**General**

GenapSys, Inc. and its related companies (“GenapSys” or “we”) respect the privacy of our customers, business partners, and other visitors to our website (“Site”). This Privacy Policy is published to help you understand what information we collect and how that information is used. This Privacy Policy applies only to the use and collection of data obtained by GenapSys through this Site.

**What information we collect**

GenapSys may collect personal information to provide you with information and services and to help us better understand your needs and interests. We may collect such personal information as your name, contact, and billing information, as well as any other information you provide us through this Site. Personal information may be required to determine access to certain restricted parts of our Site. Information collected online may be supplemented with information you provide through other sources such as trade shows or seminars. In addition, we automatically log information about you and your computer. For example, when visiting our Site, we log your computer operating system type, browser type, browser language, the website you visited before browsing to our Site, pages you viewed, how long you spent on a page, access times, and information about your use of and actions on our Site. 

**How we use collected information**

GenapSys will use personal information to provide customers and business partners with information and services and to help us better understand your needs and interests. Specifically, we use your information to help you complete a transaction or order, to communicate with you, to deliver products/services to you, to bill you for products/services you purchased, and to provide ongoing service and support. We also use your personal information to operate, maintain, and improve our sites, products, and services and to protect, investigate, and deter against fraudulent, unauthorized, or illegal activity. Occasionally we may use your information to contact you to complete surveys that we use for marketing and quality assurance purposes. 

**Sharing collected information**

We may share information with those who need it to do work for us. In addition, GenapSys may contract with third-party service providers that are required to keep confidential the personal information received from GenapSys and may not use it for any purpose other than as originally intended in accordance with this Privacy Policy. We require such third parties to comply with our Privacy Policy, and limit their access and use of your personal information. GenapSys does not provide, rent, or sell your information to third parties for marketing use. Except as described in this Privacy Policy, GenapSys will not share personally identifiable information with other third parties without your permission, unless required by, or in connection with, law enforcement action, subpoena or other litigation, or applicable law or in connection with a prospective or actual sale, merger, transfer, or other reorganization of all or parts of our business. We may also share aggregated and/or anonymized data with others for their own uses. 

**Security of your information**

GenapSys is committed to ensuring the security of the personal data you choose to provide us. We employ industry standard technical and administrative controls to protect against unauthorized access to and unlawful interception or processing of your personal information. 

**Linked websites**

Links to third-party websites that may appear on this Site are provided for your convenience and information and in no way imply any affiliation, endorsement, sponsorship, or acceptance of any information or views provided on those linked websites. If you access those links, you will leave the GenapSys Site. These third-party sites are subject to separate and independent privacy policies. We are not obligated to review such third-party sites and do not control such third-party sites. Therefore, we have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites (or any products, services, or content available through the same). We encourage you to review the privacy policy of any party before submitting your personal information. 

**Information choices and changes**

Our marketing emails tell you how to “opt out.” If you opt out, we may still send you non-marketing emails. Non-marketing emails include emails about your accounts and our business dealings with you. You may send requests about personal information to our Contact Information below. You can request to change contact choices, opt out of our sharing with others, and update your personal information. You can typically remove and reject cookies from our Site with your browser settings. Many browsers are set to accept cookies until you change your settings. If you remove or reject our cookies, it could affect how our Site works for you. 

**Applicable law**

This Privacy Policy and any and all actions, claims, disputes, or controversies relating to this Privacy Policy, the use of this Site, or any materials therein shall be interpreted according to the laws of the State of California, United States of America, without regard to its conflicts of laws provisions. By using this Site, you expressly consent to the exclusive forum, jurisdiction, and venue of the state and federal courts of San Mateo County, California, United States of America, in such actions, claims, disputes, or controversies. GenapSys makes no representations that this Site is appropriate or available for use in locations outside of the United States, and access to them from territories where their contents are illegal is prohibited. You may not use or export the materials at this Site in violation of United States export or other laws and regulations. If you choose to access this Site from locations outside the United States, you do so on your own initiative and are responsible for compliance with applicable local laws. 

**Use of Cookies**

GenapSys may use cookies in order to store user-provided information. Cookies are temporary or permanent identifiers that can be sent from a website through your browser to be placed on your computer, enabling the website to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information to enhance your user experience. You can set your browser to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. You may elect not to accept cookies by changing the settings on your web browser, but that may limit your use of some features at this Site. 

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms of Use page establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website. 

**Your consent**

By using our site, you consent to our Privacy Policy. 

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

We may modify this Privacy Policy, in whole or in part, at any time and in our sole discretion. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date above. Your continued use of this Site constitutes acceptance of this Privacy Policy as modified. 

**Contact information**

If you have questions or concerns regarding this online Privacy Policy, please contact info@genapsys.com.
